Good Morning.  You have shown strong growth of 18% in Q4.
But this
figure has remained only 7% throughout the year.  This
is slightly lower than the industry average.  Are you
losing market share or is your focus
on profit right now?
I think great question.  So first of all
thank you so much for having me in the channel
and good morning to all your viewers.  So,
I
want to answer this in context because
if you look at the growth of the industry
in the last so many years, like
when the insurance sector opened in
2001-2002, if you look at the growth till today, the
compounded growth in revenue has been
about 15-16% and the thought process of ICICI LBA
in terms of writing growth or
driving the book has been to grow the book
profitably.  So our thinking has been that
wherever we see profitable opportunities,
we obviously kind of go all
out and make sure that we are able to tap
into the opportunity and this is the
thought process which you have seen in FI
26 and your point is absolutely correct.  If you
look at the numbers for the entire year, at an aggregate
level, the industry's growth has been roughly about
9.2%. The growth of ICMR was
roughly about 7%. So, the outcome is that we
can think that ICMR has grown
slower than the market, but having said that
if you break this growth into the
first half and second half, in the first half,
our growth compared to the industry, the
industry's growth was roughly about 7%.
Our growth was absolutely, we were almost off at
a brick even level, but in the second half, I think we did see a lot
of rebound. And if you
all remember, there was a lot of
reforms that was being done on multiple
fronts.
OK Gopal ji, despite strong premium growth in Q4,
profits grew only 7%.  So are
you seeing some pressure on margins?
So if you look at the
outcome of our combined ratio, if you have
seen from quarter 4 to quarter 4 of
last year, actually there has been an
improvement of almost about 150 basis
points.  So we have actually
seen a lot of improvement in the combined issue.  But if
you talk about absolute profit, as per
our current accounting requirement,
when you collect the premium, when
we collect the premium for the entire year, at
the time of writing the risk, its earnings are
earned in the entire 12 months of the policy.  But whatever
cost you incur to source that policy,
we have to take the entire cost on day one.  So,
if you look at this absolute profit or loss situation, to that
extent you will not be able to see that it is
immediately getting
played out.  And that is a reason why and
this happens in a period when the growth is
good then all the more the reason that you will see
on an absolute basis the
absolute underwriting outcome getting
reflected differently this is the anomaly that
gets taken care of when you look at the
combined ratio numbers ICB's thinking is
that we are able to deliver a sustained ROE
return on equity for our shareholders in
the range of 18 to 20% so
this year also if you would have seen I think we
ended the year full year with an ROE of roughly about
18% on
us as you talked about your
combined ratio has improved but will it
slip below this mark of 100 in this financial year and
what is your outlook for FI 27 growth I
think crystal gazing is
very difficult in this environment but having  Said that
I
want to answer this in the context again.  The reason
is if you see the insurance business is such a
business which has to kind of looked
at over long sales.  Because there may be a big loss in some year.
Some years there can be
catastrophic events and some
years there can be some competitive
intensity playing out.  So the reason is that
if you look at the outcome of any year, it may
not be representative of the business
thought process you are running.  Yes, if you
look at the last 10 years, which we discussed in
our investor call yesterday,
if
you look at the ICC LBA combined ratio numbers for the last 10 years
with the industry, the
last 10 year average combined
ratio of the industry was about 11.15% - 115%. But if you look at the
same numbers of IC LBA over the last 10 years, the
combined ratio of ICIC LBA was
102.9%.
So clearly, the delta or the gap
between the industry combined ratio and I.
Columbus's combined ratio has been more
than 10% points and that is exactly what we want to keep
looking for. We will always continue to do better than the
industry combined ratios.
Ok.  Okay, now let me bisect your numbers a little bit
segment wise and talk about it.
Motor growth here is 7.6% which is below
industry average.  But
your growth in the commercial vehicle segment has been very strong.
37% So going forward,
what will be the growth drivers and
what growth are you seeing in both these segments?
Considering all I mean STs and the demand
and competitive environment.
So our preferred lines are it has
always been motor, it has been health and it has been
commercial lines. At an aggregate
level, these three lines are
preferred segments of businesses for ICE Lamb,
but if you break it down with motor, there is
private car, there is two wheeler,
there is commercial vehicles, then depending
on the opportunity we see in the market, is how we kind
of rebalance the
portfolio with motor and hence, if
you have seen the mix, it would be between
private car, two wheeler and commercial
vehicles.  This mix hasn't stayed consistently the same through the
years.  Because that is how you will have to
kind of change your business model
depending on the market environment you
see, you should be able to
make the change and since to that extent the
outcome will get reflected.  Similarly, if
you talk about health, for us health is
a very very strong preferred line.
Inside this there is corporate health, there is
retail health.  Corporate health is
again very opportunistic, there is a
lot of importance in pricing [clearing throat] and to that extent
we obviously do a conscious approach on retail
lines consistently, you must have seen over the
last three years we have been continuously talking about it that we want to launch
new products, we want to expand
distribution, due to this our
market share for SB is improved from
3.3% on retail health to 4.1%
okay.  Okay Gopal ji, thank you very much.
You joined the conversation after this numbers.  He
spoke on all parameters and
shared his outlook for the coming quarters.
Thank you very much.  And best of
luck.